[{"answer": "I'm good.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 14, "question": "Eva, how are you?", "qSentId": 13}, {"answer": "Lovely to have you in my studio.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 16, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 15}, {"answer": "Occupation.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "What do you mean?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "Actor is on there.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 41, "question": "What do you call yourself?", "qSentId": 40}, {"answer": "Yes, one of those things that I mentioned.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "That excites me?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "I mean like when you're older you have a better appreciation for history or for knowledge.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "Chicano studies and political science.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "What are you -- what are you actually studying?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "Chicano studies is the study mostly of the Mexican- American movement that has happened in the United States, and the history of Mexican-Americans.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "What is Chicano studies?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "Can I?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "You can be an honorary Chicano.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "You can be an honorary Chicano?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "Well, you have to help us in the fight for social justice and believe in equality for everyone.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "What do I have to do?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "Pretty important.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 83, "question": "How important are your roots to you?", "qSentId": 82}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 95, "question": "You had to learn Spanish?", "qSentId": 94}, {"answer": "I speak a bit of French.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 104, "question": "Do you speak French?", "qSentId": 103}, {"answer": "When I came here, I couldn't believe the hot issue it really is.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "Immigration?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "Well, that's a loaded question.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "How would you fix things?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "I think he had a lot on his plate.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "Do you think he has lived up to expectations?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "The great thing about this documentary is that -- actually we produced it so it can be used as a political tool to change the way agricultural workers are treated in the United States.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "It's heartbreaking to see kids having to do this in modern ages, isn't it?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "You're quite an activist, aren't you?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "You shouldn't be, but I am.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 202, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 201}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "How do you deal with that as someone who's got in your own family?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "She's doing amazing.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "How is she doing?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "I mean, to have somebody in your life who, none of that means anything to at all and who's not impressed by any of that because why would she be?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "She's very grounding.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "It makes it very natural for you, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 304, "question": "Don't you find that a bit unsettling when you go home?", "qSentId": 303}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "No entourage?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "I'm really not a complainer.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "What's the matter with you?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "I'm going to go sit in your lap.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "Do we say slouch, lay back, think of England?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "Why do you think I put you in an uncomfortable chair?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "Yes, I tweet a lot.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "Aren't you?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "You know it's funny because Demi Moore and Ashton were, like, you know, the really pioneers of getting everybody on Twitter.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "What's the attraction of Twitter?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "No, not drunk tweeting.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "Are you a drunk tweeter?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "It's more to do with putting stuff out there where you -- why did I do that?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "Like if you choose to make your life so public?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "No, because I mean -- really I don't really care.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "Because it's so easy now to become a celebrity?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "You're look like a mini Oprah, aren't you?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "Well, I think similar to Oprah.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "What's the Eva Longoria brand?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "Are you tough enough to be a mogul, do you think?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "I am not to be messed with.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "Are you not to be messed with?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "Never.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "I mean seriously, could you ever go out with a man with a soft handshake?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "I'm not going to name them now.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "Who?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "Probably my family.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "Who taught you direct eye contact and firm handshake?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "And they're all strong, strong women.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "They're all strong women, aren't they?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "They're proud.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "What do they make -- what do they make of what's happened to you?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "Well, I was always different.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "Are they -- do they quite believe it?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "Do I like being famous?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "Or does it make no difference?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "Did you imagine you would be married for life?", "qSentId": 521}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "But did you really believe this was the guy, this was the one for you for life?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "It all came out.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "The marriage?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "A bit, yes.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 578, "question": "Do you feel humiliated?", "qSentId": 577}, {"answer": "Well, you know, like I said, we just -- you want different things.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "What more could a guy want, frankly?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "Is there any way back as far as you're concerned, if a man behaves that way towards you?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 611, "question": "Do you think he wants to?", "qSentId": 610}, {"answer": "Oh, that's a horrible question to ask when I just got divorced.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 615, "question": "Would you get married again?", "qSentId": 614}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 620, "question": "It's not top of your list, is it?", "qSentId": 619}, {"answer": "Yes, we've been divorced for a while.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 624, "question": "Are you actually divorced yet?", "qSentId": 623}, {"answer": "She's 10 years younger than me.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 638, "question": "How old is your wife?", "qSentId": 637}, {"answer": "I recommend it.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 640, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 639}, {"answer": "Tell me about your --", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 648, "question": "I mean, even though she's younger?", "qSentId": 647}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 659, "question": "Do you mind when those pictures come out?", "qSentId": 658}, {"answer": "I love being in love.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 667, "question": "Do you like being in love?", "qSentId": 666}, {"answer": "Once.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 671, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love?", "qSentId": 670}, {"answer": "And I married him.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 673, "question": "And you married him?", "qSentId": 672}, {"answer": "More than that.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 679, "question": "How many times have you been in love?", "qSentId": 678}, {"answer": "Well, you did say move on, but I think we'll stick around for a while if you don't mind.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 694, "question": "What's the next subject?", "qSentId": 693}, {"answer": "You know, I thought it would -- was actually really, was really disappointed in the concept of loyalty and faithfulness and things like that, but, no, I can't let it.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 702, "question": "Has what happened to you damaged your ability to love, do you think?", "qSentId": 701}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 719, "question": "What is the way to have a civilized break?", "qSentId": 718}, {"answer": "It's still my future, I still will have children.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 737, "question": "Did that particularly worry you, that you kind of reached a point in a relationship where you were about to have children and suddenly it's not the future you thought you had?", "qSentId": 736}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 746, "question": "I mean, are you in an exclusive situation with your playboy or is there a door opening here?", "qSentId": 745}, {"answer": "It would be four.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 759, "question": "If you had a dream number, what it would be?", "qSentId": 758}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 784, "question": "Oh, really?", "qSentId": 783}, {"answer": "I love to cook.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 813, "question": "Why should I get excited by your cookbook?", "qSentId": 812}, {"answer": "Well, guacamole.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 825, "question": "Oh, it's called guac, is it, you call in the trade?", "qSentId": 824}, {"answer": "These are my signature things.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 833, "question": "Now, are these your little signature things?", "qSentId": 832}, {"answer": "I love margaritas.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 853, "question": "Now the interview starts, huh?", "qSentId": 852}, {"answer": "It's all very simple and, you know, I'm not a chef.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 857, "question": "But this is all quite simple food, isn't it?", "qSentId": 856}, {"answer": "If you can read, you can cook.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 866, "question": "Do you think there's someone watching this who can't cook, like me, if they read this book?", "qSentId": 865}, {"answer": "You know, the people you reach.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 895, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 894}, {"answer": "Sex.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 902, "question": "Oh, God, what are you going to say?", "qSentId": 901}, {"answer": "She told me that.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 915, "question": "Did she tell you that?", "qSentId": 914}, {"answer": "No, it wasn't on air, no.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 917, "question": "On air?", "qSentId": 916}, {"answer": "Good for Gwyn.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 924, "question": "None?", "qSentId": 923}, {"answer": "I am.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 931, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 930}, {"answer": "No, I don't.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 939, "question": "When you see the Oscars on TV, do you think -- do you start practicing the speech that may never happen?", "qSentId": 938}, {"answer": "I actually love --", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 946, "question": "Do you like politics?", "qSentId": 945}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 962, "question": "Can you imagine?", "qSentId": 961}, {"answer": "ONGORIA: I know.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 966, "question": "What about Oprah-Eva ticket?", "qSentId": 965}, {"answer": "You know, people ask me this all the time.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 972, "question": "What's been the moment you'd relive tomorrow if you had the chance?", "qSentId": 971}, {"answer": "Well, yes, I just did -- finished a film called \"Cristiada\" with Andy Garcia.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 991, "question": "Any movies?", "qSentId": 990}, {"answer": "In the fall.", "docId": "110723pmt", "aSentId": 997, "question": "When's it out?", "qSentId": 996}]